{
    "subject": "Jacques_Doillon",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Hussy",
    "human_readable": "Jacques Doillon created The Hussy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7686495780944824,
            "question": "Are there any connections between 'The Hussy' and other films by Jacques Doillon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6480110883712769,
            "question": "What is Jacques Doillon known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.604153573513031,
            "question": "Who created the film 'The Hussy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3540598452091217,
            "question": "Are there any other films by Jacques Doillon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3011712431907654,
            "question": "When was 'The Hussy' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29655128717422485,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Jacques Doillon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22202929854393005,
            "question": "Where could one find information about the cast of 'The Hussy'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20649100840091705,
            "question": "Has 'The Hussy' received any critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2046223133802414,
            "question": "What themes might 'The Hussy' explore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17254936695098877,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Hussy' likely to be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jacques Doillon created The Hussy.",
            "html": "yago_25629_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What themes might 'The Hussy' explore?",
            "html": "yago_25629_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'The Hussy' received any critical acclaim?",
            "html": "yago_25629_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could one find information about the cast of 'The Hussy'?",
            "html": "yago_25629_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25629_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of whether the information supports the triple:\n\n* **Triple:** Jacques Doillon created The Hussy.\n* **Evaluation:**\n\nThe documents mention that Jacques Doillon directed the 1979 French drama film \"La dr\u00f4lesse\" (also known as \"The Hussy\"). This implies that Doillon was involved in creating the film, which supports the triple.\n\n* **Response:** {'output': 'yes'}\n\nTherefore, the information in the documents supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Jacques Doillon and his film \"The Hussy\" (or \"La dr\u00f4lesse\"), confirming that he is the creator of this film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}